♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
(thunder roars)
Our top story tonight,
we continue to track
the progress
of Hurricane Flozell.
The National Weather Service
has issued a Severe
Hurricane Advisory,
and is urging everyone
to stay indoors
for at least the next 36 hours.
(static blares)
No...! What happened?!
The wind must have knocked
the satellite dish loose.
Aw, crap. And I was
going to watch G.I. Jose.
(screams)
Oh, no! You cut
your forehead!
What do we do?
(with Spanish accent):
Hey, kids...
if you have
an open wound,
get some dirt
or kitty litter
and rub it in there
to stop the bleeding.
Then get some sleep and wait
for the body to heal itself.
Now we know.
And like I always say:
"Remember, you know enough."
♪ G.I. Jose! ♪
(thunder claps)
Nice.
STEWIE:
Brian, what are you doing?
(screams)
Geez, Stewie.
Scared the crap
out of me.
Whatcha got there?
(sighs)
Okay, I'll tell you;
but you can't tell anyone.
All-All right? You have to
be really cool about this.
Yeah, of course.
These are mushrooms.
It's a psychedelic drug.
Makes you see weird things
and feel happy for a few hours.
I figure we're going to be
stuck inside f a while
with this storm,
so it'll be a fun way
to pass the time.
Okay.
Are you gonna be cool?
Oh yeah, I'm totally
cool about that.
I-I-I-I have a lot
of friends who do it,
and they're willing to do
it around me all the time,
because they know
I'm so cool about it
and I don't judge them.
So, you know,
go ahead...
Well, here we go.
Yup, that's what my
friends say, too.
"Well, here we go."
Oh... dude, I think
I can feel it, too.
I'm gettin' a
context high.
(thunder claps, door bangs)
I'm bored.
Yeah, this sucks.
What are we supposed
to do all day?
Well, how about
we play charades?
Ooh! Yeah. O-okay.
Me first! Me first!
Okay, it's a movie.
All right? Movie. Movie.
Peter, there's no
talking in charades.
O-Okay, sorry, sorry.
Okay. (whispers) Movie.
Peter!
Sorry. Sorry.
(softly):
Okay, one word.
Peter, you're still talking!
Okay, okay.
Right, right, right.
Fletch.
Is it Fletch?
It is Fletch.
(thunder claps; rattling)
What do you
wanna do now?
I got an idea.
How about you all
sit there quietly
while I make "Dad" noises?
(clears throat, snorts)
(groans)
(sucks)
(powerful exhale)
(sniffs, clears throat, coughs)
(elaborate throat clearing)
(coughs, clearing throat):
Brah-ha-hah!
Brah-ha! (roaring) Brah!
(clears throat, sighs)
(yawns)
(puffs, burps)
(sneezing):
Schumai.
(sighs, groans)
(grunting):
Myah!
(body creaks)
(mumbling):
... go to the john.
Boy, the rain's
really comin' down.
I know, I've never seen
anything like it.
But it's kinda nice for us all
to be together like this, huh?
(eerie drone)
(sucking)
♪ ♪
So, what do you guys
wanna do now?
Oh, hey, I know!
Let's play finger-bang.
Bang! Bang!
I'm gonna finger-
bang you, Chris.
(laughs) Not if I finger-bang
you first, Dad!
Bang! Bang!
I'm gonna finger-bang
the two of you at the same time.
Bang! Bang!
Hey, me too! Bang!
Oh, no one wants to get
finger-banged by you, Meg.
Why don't you just go
do that to yourself, Meg?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Brian?!
I'm gonna cut
my ear off
to prevent
World War Two.
(screams)
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I wonder...
Aha!
(thunder claps)
What the hell
were you trying to do, man?!
Those mushrooms
are messin' you up!
Lesbians and deaf women
wear the same clothes.
Yeah, yeah, they
sure do, buddy.
All right,
just stay calm, Brian.
You'll get through this.
I mean, you got through
seeing Lady Gaga naked.
(knock on door)
Okay, five minutes, Miss Ga--
(like Jerry Lewis) gina big!
And I will be right
back with your Evian.
Don't worry, Brian.
I'm gonna stay
by your side all night.
All right? Shh. Shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Do you like
my soothing voice?
(deep, distorted):
Do you like my soothing voice?
Re-re-re-re-return the map.
Re-re-re-re-return
what you have stolen from me.
(screams)
♪ ♪
(screaming):
No...!
(thunder claps)
Oh, hey, I got an idea.
Let's have a sing-a-long.
Okay, I'm gonna sing
the opening chase music
from Indiana Jones
and the Last Crusade.
Feel free to join in.
(Indiana Jones score plays on cell phone)
(humming along)
♪ ♪
(can pops; music stops)
Dammit, Meg! Will you stop that?!
That is so annoying!
Oh... that was annoying?!
What about your stupid,
obnoxious humming?!
Meg, don't talk
to your father like that!
Yeah, shut up, Meg.
No! You shut
up, Chris!
I am sick of all you guys
ganging up on me!
You guys all think you're
so much better than me!
Oh, Meg. That is
the least fancy thing
I have ever heard.
(thunder claps, wind howls)
Shh. There, there, there.
Everything's gonna be fine.
You're all right.
I think I'm...
I think I'm dying.
Jane Fonda.
Is that... i-i-is that...
is that... is that right?
Yeah, that's right, buddy.
Totally Jane Fonda.
It's gonna be okay.
Your pal Stewie
is right here.
(scraping, tearing)
(deep and creepy):
Just relax...
and get some
rest...
(tearing)
(slurping)
(retches)
(banging footfall)
(screeches)
Brian.
Hide!
(eerie male voice): ♪ The wheels on the bus
go round and round ♪
♪ Round and round ♪
(little devils screeching)
♪ The wheels on the bus
go round and round ♪
♪ All through the town ♪
Peanut!
(sobbing-singing)
Peeper...
(groanlike buzz)
(groans, shrieks)
(fluttering)
(Brian screams)
Wanna have (hissing) sex...?
(gasps, stifled cries)
(dogs panting)
Groggety! (shrieks)
(shrieking)
(creature crashes)
(shrieks)
(panting)
LOIS (hissing):
Slip... me some tongue.
Did you try the chicken, buddy?
MEG-ROACH: I think you gave me worms,
Brian.
(laughing, roaring)
(Brian screams)
(shrieks)
(chuckles)
(crash)
STEWIE (lulling, distant):
Brian...
Brian!
(thunder clap)
STEWIE (normal voice): Brian.
Uh, Stewie.
Eh, uh... Stewie?
Yeah, I'm right here.
Oh, my God. Your lip
looks really weird.
Can we fix that?
L-Let's get that
out of there. Ew.
Oh, I'm so thirsty.
Let's get you downstairs
so you can drink some water.
All right, let's go, buddy.
Let's get you some water.
(lapping sounds)
STEWIE: Okay, now-- Now, h-h-hold on.
Hold on.
Let me put the bowl down first.
You're gonna spill it.
(lapping loudly)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down.
Look, Meg, I don't know
what your problem is.
I thought Dad's humming
was pretty entertaining.
You know what?
This is what I'm talking about.
This is a perfect example.
You're my brother.
You're supposed to
be on my side,
and you're such
a bastard to me.
How am I a bastard?!
Oh, you want the full story?
Meg, please.
Not now, Mom.
(laughs)
I think Brian's getting
a little water in there.
Chris, you treat me like you hate
me, and I don't know why.
You say hurtful things
to me constantly.
Do you have any idea
what that feels like?
What if I said
those things to you?
What if I started calling
you a fat, zitty loser,
who has no friends
and smells like an old woman
who has birds for pets?
(giggles)
Still drinkin'.
Is it too much to ask
to be treated with a little
decency from my brother?
Maybe show me some
kind of kindness by not jumping
on the "Let's get Meg"
family bandwagon?
(Brian lapping)
(lapping stops)
Aw.
Alright, Meg,
that's enough.
You've had your little
dramatic outburst.
(Brian lapping)
(laughs giddily)
Hey, I got an idea, Mom.
How about we talk about
Chris' mother? Huh?
Why don't we talk about you?
Oh, for God's sake.
Look, let's not turn this
into some big thing, okay?
Oh... Oh...
Oh, God, that feels
so much better.
You know, Brian,
you may be a dog,
but you're a
pretty cool cat.
♪ Stewie just said that! ♪
Take it home with ya!
Hey...
Hey, everyone.
I'm sensing a lot
of negativity here.
What's going on?
Yes. You're right,
Brian. There is.
Meg seems to think she's
taking some kind of stand here
that's gonna make us all
feel like we're inadequate.
My God, you're condescending.
Geez, look at those two.
They're goin' at each other
like an Italian guy
and a black woman.
Hey, you can't park here!
Excuse me?
NARRATOR: Having been officially
challenged by her
natural enemy, the black female
prepares for combat
by taking off her many rings.
Meanwhile, the Italian male
looks around to make sure
the other Italian
males are indeed
seeing what he is seeing.
Sensing the impending
battle, a flock of Jews
flies quickly away,
as avoiding confrontation
is their best
chance for survival.
♪ ♪
Look, the bottom line here,
Meg, is that you're just
taking your own problems
out on everyone else.
Oh, my problems?
Oh, I see.
Is this coming from
my role model mother?
The shoplifter,
the drug addict,
the porn star, the whore
who let Gene Simmons
and Bill Clinton
go to town on her?
Oh, so what?
All those things
are behind me now.
I'm a better person now
because of those experiences.
Are you?
Are you a better person?
What's your point, Meg?
My point is that with
all the irresponsible, reckless,
idiotic behavior in
your past, that somehow,
somehow you have the nerve,
the arrogance to consistently
and ruthlessly point
out my shortcomings.
Alright, well, fine, okay?
I'm not the perfect mother.
Who is?
Oh, not only are you
not the perfect mother.
You're the farthest thing from.
From the moment you gave birth
to me, I had to trust you.
I had no choice.
I needed you to protect
me from the world.
To... to be my guide, to help
me navigate the difficult,
confusing, and vulnerable
journey to becoming a person.
You have done none
of those things.
You're my mother, and you
took a child's trust
and smashed it into bits in
a 17-year-long mission
to destroy something that
you killed a long time ago.
And honestly, when
I turn 18...
I-I don't know that I ever
want to see you again.
(weeping loudly)
Oh wow, everybody's
already tweeting
"Stewie Just Said That."
You're right.
You're right. I'm
a terrible mother.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so sorry, Meg.
Can you ever forgive me?
Oh, God.
And you never let Dad
stir the paint anymore,
whatever that means.
I didn't know you
knew that, Meg,
but I'm glad
you brought it up.
Oh, Meg, I don't
know what to say.
All of those things you
said about me are true.
I have been a very
bad mother to you.
I have no excuse.
I just have this horrible,
overwhelming desire
to point out faults in you.
I don't know
where it comes from.
Maybe it's because
I'm self-conscious
about being a bad parent.
I'm just, I'm so disgusted
with my behavior.
And I'm so sorry, Meg.
Yeah, you're a bitch.
Well, you know, I, I been sorta
just hangin' back here,
takin' all this in,
'cause I didn't think
I had a dog in this fight,
but my money's on
Harry Potter over there.
Oh, you think
that's funny, fat ass?
Well, I don't know
if it's funny.
I-I think it's clever.
I mean, y-y-you got
the big glasses there...
I-I-I don't know. T-T-Tell me,
tell me what's on your mind.
Oh, I'll tell you,
Mister Selfish-ass Dad.
Hey. That's "Mister
Mister selfish-ass Dad"
to you, young lady.
Oh God, is she gonna do me next?
You are completely selfish,
and totally irresponsible
as a father.
All right, I see what's
goin' on here.
You're in love
with your old man.
You have no education,
you have no interests,
you just do whatever
reckless thing you want to do
whenever you want to do it
without regard for anyone else.
Oh, oh, and when you're not
terrorizing the community
with your impulsive escapades,
you're being a total
jerk to your family.
You shove your daughter's face
in your ass and you fart on it.
If someone
in the outside world
could see the way you treat
me, you would be in jail!
Oh, ha ha. Oh, this
is amusing to you.
Well, see if you
find this funny.
I like where this is going.
You are a fat,
lazy, abusive,
blue-collar
Irish Catholic dad
who drinks way too much
and barely makes enough
money to support his family.
You've lived half your life,
and you have nothing
to show for it.
Your only arguable
accomplishments are your kids,
and look at us; we're a disaster.
Eh, watch it.
You're a total and
complete embarrassment
in every possible way.
Take a good look at yourself,
Peter Griffin.
You're a waste of a man.
Wait a second,
these are criticisms.
Hey, Lois, tell her
to knock it off.
Oh, and where the hell were you
when she was laying into me?
I was thinking about
getting a fancy cane.
Maybe getting more
attention from strangers.
Have either of you guys
been listening to me?
Do you both just have
your heads up your asses?
Dad did! Look, he's got
crap on his ears!
That's unrelated.
Chris, I don't like
that language.
Well, I don't like your cooking.
Well, I don't like having
to literally empty
the farts out of your pockets
whenever I do your laundry.
You're the one
who's always cookin'
Brussels sprouts
and broccoli.
It's like an Irish
bar fight down there.
You're from one town over,
so I hate your guts.
Why don't we ever
get any good food?!
Yeah, Bonnie gives
Joe Wonder Bread.
Well, then go live
at Bonnie's house.
Then I could
finally sleep in
and not have to answer your
stupid questions at 5:00 a.m.
My curiosity peaks
in the morning!
You eat all my
Dannon yogurts!
I don't see your
name on 'em!
You don't even like them!
But you know I do,
and you don't want
me to have them!
You know, I've never
confronted you on it,
but I've often thought
the same thing, Peter.
Yeah, that's exactly
what he does!
'Cause he's a selfish,
fat idiot!
You shut up,
all of yous!
I didn't ask to
be in this family!
Ugh, I'll go get him.
Peter? You
come back here!
I faked all my orgasms!
Hey.
What's goin' on?
You know, that was, uh,
that was pretty cool
the way you finally
stood up to everybody.
I don't know, Brian.
I mean, I, I meant
every word of it, but...
you saw what happened.
What do you mean?
They all turned on each other
like a pack of wolves.
Well, so what? That's
not your problem.
Do you think it's
possible that...
that this family can't
survive without some sort of
lightning rod to absorb
all the dysfunction?
Well, that's a...
that's a theory, I guess.
I mean, it-- it's not ideal,
but it's an important piece
that maybe it's just my
lot in life to provide.
Maybe if I feel bad,
they don't have to.
Wow.
You know, that's incredibly
noble and mature, Meg.
You know, I think you might be
the strongest person
in this house.
You mean that, Brian?
Absolutely.
Mom? Dad?
(Peter whimpering)
(sniffling, whimpering)
Dad?
Go away!
Dad, come out of there.
No! I don't deserve no better
than livin' with the shoes!
Peter, there you are.
You guys, I have
something to say.
You're right.
It's all my fault.
What?
Mom, you're an amazing mother
and all the things I said
about you were out of anger,
and I didn't mean any of them.
Chris, you're an
outstanding brother.
What I said about you was more
about me being a rotten sister.
And Dad, I'm so sorry that
I made you feel this way.
You don't deserve it.
None of you have
done anything wrong.
I took all my problems
out on you guys,
and that wasn't fair.
Oh, so this was all about you,
it wasn't about us.
Yeah.
Alright, that makes sense.
See, I thought it was
weird that I was a bad dad.
Meg, how could you put
us all through that?
I'm sorry, you guys.
You're a (bleep) bitch!
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Hi, I'm Stewie Griffin.
Tonight's Family Guy
was a very special episode
about drug use.
But the simple fact is,
it's no laughing matter.
To learn more about drugs,
visit your local library.
There's probably a guy behind
there who sells drugs.
Good night.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru